http://www.bca.org/privacy.html

Past Presidents
F.A.Q.
Privacy Policy
The BCA is committed to protecting your privacy on many different levels.
Website
We do not collect personal information to sell on this website. We may collect data in order to improve this site. We will not release any of your personal data to any third party unless required by law. By accessing this site, you are consenting to only the information collection and use that will help BCA serve you better.
BCAtalk
The inherent public nature of this forum dictates that the BCA assumes no responsibility for protecting the information disclosed on it by users. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in public forums.
Mailing Lists
Postal mailing lists, comprised of full name, email, and postal address, may be sold to other organizations (e.g. professional societies and/or commercial vendors) for one-time promotional or informational use. Promotional or informational materials are subject to BCA approval prior to the rental. If you want your name deleted from this list please contact the Director of Member Services at office@bca.org.
Copyright
Copyrights for images or materials on this website are held by the contributors. Any use of these images or materials without getting permission beforehand is illegal and subject to prosecution.
The BCA privacy statement is subject to change and was created on November 3, 2005.
Related Links
Professional Resources
Membership
Annual Meeting
Home  |  Image Credits  |  Privacy Policy  |  Downloads  |  Member Login  |  Contact© BioCommunications Association
Sign up for BCA email
